Subscribe to your technical
channel and press the bell icon to be the
first to see the latest technology videos. So
how are you? Hello friends, my
name is Armaan and you will see the technical
channel. In today's video, I will
tell you how to download HD movies.
Yes friends, many
times it happens that some movies are launched
in India, but we are not
able to download them. We do not go to the cinema hall. This is
also happening in this world, so you
can download Surasa in your phone and
watch HD movies and get entertainment.
This movie is available online. Movies are also
launched on it, so you can wait for 20 minutes.
Many times it happens that you
find many websites on which we
start downloading, but those movies are not downloaded.
Let's start. Friends,
in this video I will tell you how you
can download the desired movies and you can stay forever. So,
my name is Hanuman and you are watching the
channel to watch, so let's
start. If you like the video, then
subscribe to the channel and
share it as much as possible. Thank you.
So first of all, we leave.  Google Chrome,
after going here you have to search for
Vidmate, this is an application, it will
not be available on the Google Play Store, it has been
removed from the Google Play Store, so
you can see that
you will find this application available on many websites,
you will find many different applications in it
and I am giving the link in the description,
you can easily download it from there,
if you are not able to understand it on Google then
I have already installed it, so
let me open it,
after opening you will see some such
interface, you can see that there are many
movies here, here you have to
click on movies, here there are many
picture statuses, but you have to click on movies,
here you can see that you are
going to Mumbai, by clicking on it
you can download from electricity, so let me assume that if you want to
download these movies then by
clicking on download you
can download Nirjali here, but your internet
should be fast,
if you are downloading from your mobile device then it will be a
little slow  But it will be done,
you can leave it after downloading it.
If you
like this video, then subscribe to the channel
and share it as much as possible. Thank
you.